Since the game began, a
whole month has gone by.
And 2,000 people have died so far.
After all this time, none of the
players have been able to clear Floor 1.
I used to be a beta tester, and even I
haven't found out where the boss's lair is.
And today, finally,
we're having a meeting to figure out how
to find and defeat the floor one boss.
Miss ni koha Cait ta u,
shiro no shibu kagejit wo ima ni.
Utsus isu isu no
sora wo Cait koko
wa Cait hakanai koko wo Mito Sheyta.
I can't live in the heart.
If your body is free.
I'm going to bring you up.
I'm looking for short future.
I'm about to spread out.
I'm willing to feel you.
I'm gonna be able to pray.
To the light in your world.
I've been to the strong witness.
Okay, people, now that everyone's here?
Let's get this meeting started.
So anyway, I want to thank everyone
for coming. Good to see you.
My name is Diabel, and in this
game, the job I rolled is night.
Dude, there's no job system in this game.
You guys want to hear this or not?
Right.
Anyway, here's the deal.
Our party found the boss room
at the top of the tower today.
First, we need to defeat the
boss and make it to floor two.
The next step is,
we have to tell everyone
waiting in the Town of
Beginnings that it is
possible to beat this game.
Fact is, it's our duty as the
most capable players here.
Do you agree or not?
Okay, glad to hear you're
all with me on this.
Now, let's figure out how
we're gonna beat the boss.
First off, we'll team
up into parties of six.
A typical party doesn't stand
a chance against a floor boss.
We need a raid group made
up of multiple parties.
Let's do this.
You got left out too, huh?
Not even.
I wasn't left out.
It's just everyone seems
like they're already friends.
So you're Solo, too.
You want to form a party with me?
You heard what the guy just said,
we can't beat the boss on our own,
and it would only be for this fight.
All right!
Looks like everyone's teamed up. Now then!
Hold up a sec!
My name's Gabe. Got that?
Before we take on the boss, I want
to get something off my chest.
We all know about the 2,000
people who've died so far, yeah?
Well, some of you need to
apologize to him right now.
Gabe, I think I know
who you're referring to.
You mean the ones who are
ex-Beta testers, right?
Of course I mean them.
The day this stupid-ass game started, the
Beta guys just up and vanished, right?
Right, they ditched all us beginners.
They snagged all the good hunting spots,
and they grabbed all the easy quests too.
They were the only ones
getting stronger in here.
This whole time they've
ignored us like we're nothing.
Hell, I bet there's some of them here.
Come on out beta testers.
We should make them apologize to us.
And we should make them all give up
their money and the items they got.
They can't expect the party to
trust them when they don't trust us.
Why should we?
Can I say something?
Hey, my name's Egyu. Gabe, right?
I want to make sure I'm on the same page.
You say the ex-beta testers
should be blamed for
the rookies' deaths because
they didn't help them.
And you want them to apologize
and give up their winnings.
I leave anything out?
No, you didn't.
the item store hands these out for free
it's a guidebook you got one didn't you sure
i got one so what about it you know who
was handing these out the ex-beta testers
listen up everyone had
equal access to this
information even so lots
of players still died now i
didn't come here to point
fingers at anyone i'm here
because i want to learn
from those player's deaths.
I'm here because I want to find out
how we're going to beat the boss.
Okay.
Can we get back to the meeting now?
For info on the boss, it's all in here.
The latest issue of the
guidebook you just heard about.
According to the book, the boss's
name is Illfang the Kobold Lord.
Also, he'll be surrounded by his
minions, the Ruin Kobold Sentinels.
Illfang carries an axe and a buckler.
He has four health bars, and
when the last one turns red,
he switches to a curved
sword-type weapon called a Talwar.
He can change his patterns of attack, too.
That's it for the briefing.
As for the distribution of loot, money
will be divided equally among everyone.
The party that defeats
the boss gets the XP,
and whoever gets an item gets to keep it!
Any objections?
Good!
We leave tomorrow at 10 in the morning.
Meeting adjourned, people!
Those are pretty good, aren't they?
Mind if I sit down?
You really think these taste good, uh?
—Huh, since I came to this town, I end
up eating at least one a day course.
I got a trick to make it taste better.
What trick?
Try it with some of that?
Cream?
I got it from the Heifer Strikes Back.
That's the quest in the village
before you get to this one.
You want to know how I did it?
Mama.
I appreciate the offer, but I didn't
come to this town to eat good food.
Okay.
Why are you here?
So I don't lose sight of who I am.
I don't want to lock myself in a room in
the town of Beginnings and slowly rot away.
I'd rather stay the way I
am till the last moment.
Even if a monster beats me and I die, I
won't lose to this game or this world,
no matter what.
I wouldn't want a party member dying
on me, so try not to die tomorrow.
Let's go over it again.
We're the backup,
so our target's gonna be the boss's
minions, the Rue and Kobold Sentinels.
I know.
I'll use a sword skill to knock
their weapons up and out of the way.
When I do, switch and jump in.
What's a switch?
Okay, level with me.
Is this the first time
you've ever been in a party?
Uh-huh.
Listen up, everyone.
I've only got one thing to say to you.
Let's win!
Come on!
Commence attack!
Squads A and C, switch it!
Here it comes!
Squad B, block!
Squad C, keep guarding
and prepare to switch.
Everyone else, when you fall
back, regroup and flank them.
Squads D, E, and F, keep those
minions off us! Yeah, you got it!
Switch!
I'm on it!
I thought she was a beginner,
but she's got good skills.
I can't even see the tip of her sword.
Right on.
Looks like the guidebook
was right. Stand back!
I got it!
I thought the plan was for everyone
in the group to surround it.
That's not a Talwar!
It's a Nodachi!
This isn't like the Beta!
Wait, stop!
It's no good! Get out of there!
Diabel, no!
Diabel!
What the hell were you thinking?
You know, you were a beta
tester too, weren't you?
You were after the last
attack bonus, the rare item.
You're just like me, a beta tester.
Please, you have to...
defeat the boss...
for everyone here.
When this death game started,
the only thing I thought about
was how I was gonna survive.
Nothing else mattered.
Take care, I'll be seeing you, Klein.
But you weren't like that, diabel—you
never abandoned the other players.
You brought them together, you led
everyone and you fought brilliantly.
brilliantly You tried to
accomplish something I couldn't.
I'll go, too.
Okay.
We'll hit him just like
we did the minions.
You got it.
Switch!
Asuna!
She's coming back!
Uh… Uh…
Ah!
No!
We can hold this bastard off
until your health's back up.
You got it.
Watch out!
You're going down!
Come on, Asuna!
Help me beat this sucker!
One last attack! You got it!
What are you talking about?
Come on, baby!
Yes!
Come on!
We ain't gonna put nothing on us!
Nice job.
That was some fine swordsmanship.
Congratulations.
Today's victory is all thanks to you.
No.
Stop cheering!
Why'd you do it, huh?
Why'd you let Diabel die?
Let him die?
That's what I said. Admit it.
You knew the technique
the boss was going to use.
You could have told us.
Then Taboo would have stood a chance.
He wouldn't have had to die.
I know why he knew.
He used to be a beta tester.
Think about it.
He knew the boss's attack patterns.
He knew, but he kept it from us.
And I bet he's not the
only beta tester here.
Come on, show yourselves!
This is bad at this
rate for everyone here.
Oh.
Hey, calm down.
So you guys think I used
to be a beta tester?
It's not cool to put me in the
same class with those noobs!
What'd you say?
You heard me.
Most of the thousand people who scored
a slot in SAO's beta were rookies.
They were so green, they didn't
even know how to level up.
Hell, even you guys are
better than they were.
But me, I'm nothing like those guys, man.
During the beta, I made it to floors that
were higher than any of the other testers.
That's a fact.
I knew about the boss,
because I fought tons of monsters with
way more sword skills on higher floors.
I know a bunch of other things, too.
More than you can imagine.
More than any info broker.
What the hell?
If that's true, then you're
worse than a beta tester.
You're a goddamn cheater!
That's what you are!
He's a beta tester and a cheater!
He's a beater!
A beater?
Yeah, that's good. I like it.
Okay.
You can call me a beater.
Just make sure you don't confuse
me with those beta testers anymore.
Wait!
When we were fighting the
boss, you called me by my name.
I wasn't trying to be rude.
Did I mess up the pronunciation?
How'd you even know it?
If you look right about here, you'll
see another HP gauge under yours.
There's a name written
right next to it, yeah?
Kirito.
Kirito?
Your name's Kirito. Yeah.
I'm so dumb.
It was there the whole
time and I never knew.
You can become powerful here on your own.
But if the day comes when someone you
trust invites you to join a guild,
don't turn it down.
Because there are limits to
what a solo player can do.
But you're solo.
I don't know. Thank
you
very
much.
Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah.
I'm not the same as my dream.
I'm the first one in
the front of the world.
I'm not the same as my dream.
I'm still going to get the same way.
I'm still on the edge.
I'm still
on the edge.
Next time, Red-Nosed Reindeer.